Episode 1
100 meters depth.
Battery check.
Oxygen pressure check.
No abnormalities in each part.
Operation normal.
How was the live broadcast, Erii?
I'm tired of it.
And I'm sleeping.
What?
It's okay, right, Karen-senpai?
You won't get fat if you eat that much.
I wonder if she's eating all the nutrients in her body.
Hey, what do you think, Aika?
It doesn't matter, so get on the seat properly.
Or you'll shake.
Here she comes.
What? What's going on?
I think she's stuck in the middle of the sea.
It's okay, right?
Leave it to me.
That's why you're worried!
Hey!
The sun shines on my heart
It's going to shine on the blue sky
If I close my eyes, I'll see the gap in my memory
The nostalgic wind of that time blew
Even if your smile is so painful that it makes me cry
Even if it looks like it's going to burst, I'm going to go beyond the present
We were born in a time when we couldn't go back
Even if tears are waiting for the future passing by
I'll hold on to the feelings I can't let go
I'll believe in that endless love and keep walking
The waves have calmed down, but...
Karen-senpai is amazing.
There's light ahead!
What? What?
Look over there. There's red light and white light.
What's that?
I don't know...
At this distance, it's a bit...
An airport?
That's right!
The captain said there was an airport!
And there's even a light!
It feels good, it feels good!
Is someone there?
I think so.
Who?
I don't know.
Well, let's look into that.
Let's look into that.
Please follow the green light.
It's green! It's green!
Look! Over there! Over there!
Shut up! I know it!
It's like a secret base.
The smell of adventure is popping!
It's popping!
Look! Speed up! Speed up!
Full speed ahead!
Shut up for a bit, you idiot.
It's a field.
There's a structure that looks like a cube in front of it.
Inside, there's an opening that looks like a vertical hole.
Go inside that.
Roger.
Now, we've entered a vertical hole!
It started again.
When it comes to vertical holes,
it reminds me of the Tateyama Shiki Jyukyo,
but I just remembered it,
so please don't mind.
The submarine will slowly, slowly dry up.
It started at level 1,
and now it's at level 6!
It's going to dive!
It's so noisy.
Speed up.
Just below.
20.
15.
That's close.
Speed up.
3.
2.
1.
Stop.
It's finally at level 9.
Oh, look at that!
There's a shutter open.
It's a mystery!
We, Shinkai Eri and the Nakayoshi Adventure Team,
have no choice but to go inside!
What do you mean, Nakayoshi Adventure Team?
It's pitch black inside!
Listen.
It's fine, right?
It's not you!
Geez.
Tateyama Shiki Jyukyo
Here we are!
Let's get off.
Don't panic.
I'll analyze the air.
What are you doing?
It's in order!
You're late!
Anyway, let's get out of here.
No!
I said no!
We're stuck.
This is it.
Wait!
It's open.
What's this?
It's an oki-tsuru.
Here, Karen-senpai.
Wait a minute.
Wait a minute!
What?
You're so reckless that you're trying to push the button.
I don't know what kind of place this is.
It's fine.
It's not fine!
What if something happens?
What are you going to do if something happens?
I know about this place.
You know about it?
This facility was also written on Karen-senpai's butterfly tattoo.
I've never heard of that.
This is the first time we've talked about it.
Tell me everything you know.
Right now!
It hurts!
What are you going to do?
Just tell me!
It hurts!
What's that sound?
No!
Let's go back!
What are you doing here?
It's dangerous!
Karen-senpai?
I'm going!
A few decades ago, a life form was attached to a meteorite that fell to Earth.
That life form was able to make humans its host and continue to live.
I've seen a movie like that before.
Humans, who became their host, slow down their physical growth, but their brain develops significantly faster.
No.
Their brain develops.
I can see it now.
The door is slightly open.
Someone is...
Go! Aika!
Why me?
It's because it's dangerous.
Go! I'm not a dog!
I'm not a dog!
I knew it.
Aika, do you remember the pattern on that door?
That's right.
It was attached to the women who attacked us on the beach.
That was like this too.
I can't ignore this relationship.
In that case, this is the last door, the door of truth!
That's it, Karen-senpai.
Is that so?
Why is it like that?
Then, senpai, this way.
Then, I'm going!
Huh?
What is it?
That's strange.
Karen-senpai should have the key.
As expected of Mystery.
Mystery is your head!
You can't open it like this!
It's not that easy.
Hey!
What are you going to do if something happens?
I'm doing it to cause something.
This is it.
Bingo!
This is it!
This is the keyhole that opens the door of truth!
A keyhole?
Then, please.
Huh?
A anesthetic?
I see.
Roger.
What are you going to do with that?
I'm going, Karen-senpai.
Erii...
What are you going to do?
The door of truth will be opened by the sleeping butterfly.
I'll leave the rest to Yoshina.
Erii...
Help me.
What are you doing?
I'm taking off my clothes.
Huh? Why?
The scanner must be reading a date from the body, such as the surface of the body.
If that's the case, the clothes are in the way, right?
Is that true?
I told you to leave the rest to Yoshina.
Come on, hurry up.
You didn't have to take everything off, did you?
I have to wear it perfectly.
Anyway, it's a beautiful shape.
I'm really envious.
Erii...
What?
No, it's nothing.
Come on, let's put Karen-senpai in the scanner.
That's the kind of club it is.
It started moving.
What?
It opened.
Hey, you!
What are you doing?
It opened!
Karen-senpai, it opened.
Wow, it's huge!
It's huge!
Wow!
What is this?
What is the relationship between this place and Karen-senpai?
You idiot!
You came here to know that, didn't you?
Well...
Don't call me an idiot!
What are you doing?
I was wondering if there was something in it, so I'm looking for it.
Isn't it better to look over there?
There are so many numbers.
It's research data.
I'm getting dizzy.
Erii, you're a good-for-nothing, aren't you?
Idiot!
Why don't you take the copy home and show it to someone who knows?
I'll take a closer look.
The meter is the same.
Didn't you say that the space life form makes humans the host?
Huh?
Yes, I did.
There's no possibility that Karen-senpai is the host.
Right?
I see.
If she's the host, then she's obviously developed.
Aha.
So that's why she's known as Father A.
This is where she develops.
Here.
Oh, a photo!
It looks like they're comparing several cells.
They all look the same.
A clone!
A clone?
That's right! It's a clone cell!
They made a clone from the host's cell and studied it!
But why?
The host will grow slower.
In other words, it means that it will slow down aging.
That's true.
And the brain develops, so the brain gets better.
If you can use that cell and use it for humans...
The world will change.
History too.
But the research on dreams didn't work out.
This is modern alchemy.
No, that's not what I meant.
If we ask an expert on this, we might be able to find out more.
That's what I said earlier.
We have to get Karen out of the scanner.
Good grief.
What's that weird voice?
Karen-senpai?
No, it's not Karen-senpai!
And...
Karen-senpai is growing!
No, it's a clone!
A clone...
I see.
Oh, it's us!
They attacked us!
We want to eliminate the host.
Oh no!
Eve, run!
Hurry!
Are you still going?
I don't know what you're talking about.
As expected of you, Icarus!
It's really small.
Move, or you'll get hurt.
Eri!
Ow, ow, ow...
That's right. Eri is...
Don't touch my friend!
Aika...
Eri, nice!
I was careless because it was so small.
It's better to be careful.
I'm a little...
What?
What's wrong?
No, no!
Eri!
What's that?
Is that a clone too?
It's not a joke!
Hurry, hurry!
Eri!
Thank you.
Aika!
Wake up!
Kuroi-senpai is...
Kuroi?
Ow, ow, ow...
Eri!
That's...
Kuroi?
That's right.
I was made here too.
Yes.
Let's go home.
Those people...
They seem to fall asleep again.
I'm going to sleep.
It's disappearing.
Good night.
That's right, Eri!
It's a shame that you couldn't get the treasure of adventure.
Huh?
I got it.
What?
This is it!
Isn't it amazing?
Two shots with the huge Kallen-senpai!
So this is what you were taking.
I took it.
This is a foot, right?
Isn't it nice?
It's subtle.
What do you mean it's subtle?
That was close, Mr. Salvager.
Thank you for the rescue, Captain!
If you die, I won't die for nothing.
Captain, are you in the infirmary?
Gast, you look like a young lady.
Watch your words.
Oh, I'm sorry!
My memories...
...were not real.
Let's make it!
Let's make a lot of memories from now on!
Thank you.
Did you enjoy your trip?
Huh? What are you talking about?
It seems you enjoyed it.
I was able to see the results of what I did.
It's better if you can see the front.
Huh?
You didn't enjoy it enough?
Huh? That's strange.
I was looking at it properly.
Well, there were a lot of things, but this first job was a great success!
Kallen-senpai's smile was a great salvage!
There was a little mystery left, but I'll figure it out someday!
That's it!
This is a piece of cake!
Yes, I'm late.
Eri, it's you!
Oh, Kallen-senpai.
Good morning.
Good morning, senpai.
But I'm late.
It's not just a little.
Just a little is not enough.
Oni!
Say whatever you want, you're late!
Dr. Risako!
There are two people who are late today!
Both of you, come to the infirmary later.
I'll tell you what happened the other day.
Go ahead.
No one will believe it.
Kallen-senpai!
Senpai, say something to that evil teacher!
Good morning.
Yes, good morning.
It's okay.
What's okay? You're late!
It's not like that!
I swear on tomorrow!
That's why the next episode is a physical examination.
That's it!