Episode 1
The depth is 150 meters.
It's flowing to the left.
Ah!
Feel the movement of the body with your body.
The enemy's display is slightly delayed.
Yes!
It's late. Look to the left.
Ah!
Even a person like you can get a C-class license.
Salveja is also getting slimmer.
If you're thinking too much, I'll do it again.
I'm not thinking.
Find out the results of your own investigation.
Feel it with your body. With your body.
That's mean.
The sun awakens.
It's in my heart.
I aim for the blue sky.
If I close my eyes,
I can see the light of my memories.
I can see the gap of my memories.
The nostalgic wind of that time blew.
Your smile is so painful.
Even if tears fall,
I'll overcome the present even if I'm about to burst.
We were born in a time when we couldn't go back.
No matter what is waiting for us in the future passing by Ashimaya,
I'll hold on tightly to my unwavering feelings.
I believe in that endless love and keep walking.
Thank you for watching.
Kikokoko...
Oh no! The timer is off!
Good morning!
I couldn't make it to the homeroom again.
Sumeragi-san, you promised me that you'd punish me if I was late.
Yes, Ms. Risako.
Then, after school, wipe the windows of the school building.
Of course, all of them.
All of them? No way!
Sumeragi-san, how many days do you think you'll be late today?
Well, I think...
Maybe five days?
If you count the days of school, you'll be late for 30 days in a row.
Oh, that's not bad.
It's not bad.
Oh, come on.
If you're still in the homeroom, you're Ryo, aren't you?
You're right in front of me.
I'm sorry again.
Hey, don't fool around like that again.
You're being too serious.
Wipe the windows and reflect on yourself.
Okay.
I guess I can't help it. I'm sleepy.
But Mel is growing up.
Well...
I'm just getting started.
I'll find your treasure.
I'm a professional, so leave it to me.
I'll accept your request fee according to your budget.
First, I'll give you advice.
One, two, A, Sumeragi, A, cut.
I wonder if he'll come soon.
The first request.
What?
C class is true.
Mel!
You want to see everything with this?
Everything?
Hey, what are you doing?
I can't overlook it as a class member.
Class membership has nothing to do with it.
How much did you work hard yesterday?
You can't just do business at school.
If you do this, the image of Class A will get worse.
I'll dismiss you as a class member.
Give it back.
I won't.
No.
Give it back.
Fine, I'll put it on again.
Then I'll take it off again.
I'll put it on so you can't take it off.
I'll put it on like this.
What?
That's enough.
Teacher, listen to me.
You.
Class is starting.
Go back to class.
You look like you're having fun.
What are you doing here? Are you here to laugh?
Come with me.
I'll tell you when I get there.
Treasure Hunting Club
I didn't know there was a club like this.
Did you make it?
I'm the director.
I didn't know there was a hobby like this.
A culture that has been eradicated from history.
Disappeared technology.
Art that I've never seen.
Art.
A sleeping treasure.
Isn't it romantic?
So what do you want from me?
That one.
Yes, Miss Eri.
Miss!
Oh, you didn't know?
This is also a history.
A history?
What's with that look?
I guess I should stop asking.
I'm counting on you.
A small submarine of the deep sea industry.
It's not a beluga.
I like it a lot.
If it's a C-class Salvager, you can control it, right?
Of course.
If it's a class like this, you can close your eyes and sleep.
The depth of sea at this time of year is good for the shape of the butt.
Do you want to ride it?
I'm asking if you want to control it.
Are you going to let me control it?
All right.
It's decided.
Let's start.
Yes, Miss Eri.
Let's start the adventure.
The departure is on the weekend.
Nice to meet you.
On the weekend?
No way.
Seriously?
Seriously.
I'm expensive.
Are you going to make money in club activities?
You want to ride the submarine, don't you?
What are you looking for?
Excuse me.
Please.
How is it?
How?
As you can see.
It's a club like that.
Is it a club like that?
What are you saying?
It's not.
Look carefully.
I don't have that kind of hobby.
We don't either.
What?
Are you saying stupid things?
Here.
It's Joda.
Joda
It's a number.
It's interesting, isn't it?
I found it.
I don't know until I tell Miss Eri.
I don't know what you're talking about.
I don't know.
I didn't know until Miss Eri told me.
I see.
Then this butterfly wasn't drawn by you, was it?
Maybe.
Maybe?
What does it mean?
It doesn't mean anything in numbers.
If you convert this number into a matrix and convert it into a row.
It becomes a row of alphabets that doesn't make sense at all.
But if you look closely, it's inside.
The door to the truth will be opened by the sleeping butterfly.
And this.
The depth and the diameter.
As expected.
Does that mean it's heading to this place?
Yes.
The answer must be here.
The mystery that calls the mystery.
I'm so excited.
Hey, everyone.
Yes, boss.
I'm going to solve the mystery and tell the story of the butterfly.
What a strange club.
Anyway, it's a great ship.
Eri was really a great person.
Yeah.
Then wouldn't it be nice if you paid for it?
The amount of commission.
I'm so rich.
My father told me not to waste my money.
Waste?
Huh?
There it is.
You really like machines, don't you?
I'm annoyed by your way of saying that.
Miss.
Captain, what's wrong?
Please come with me.
Please come in, teacher.
Oh, thank you, boy.
What's your name?
G-G-G-G-Gust.
Oh, that's a rare name.
G-G-G-G-Gust-kun.
No, that's...
Just like that.
It's not going to work.
Please do something.
Mr. Risako is really...
By the way, why did you come with me?
Because I'm a commoner of Trehanbun.
Commoner?
Oh, it's a seal.
Everyone should just die.
The island.
It existed before the disaster.
It sank.
So you're going to investigate that sinking island.
What kind of place was it?
Was there some kind of facility?
There was an airport.
Airport?
Hey, I've told you many times.
Yes, yes.
I know.
If something happens, I'll take care of it right away.
I have a duty to return you safely to your father.
Excuse me, what do you mean?
Yes.
This area is a pretty ugly area.
No matter what happens, it's not strange.
Ugly?
There's a lot.
It's a kind of modern Bermuda Triangle.
Manok area.
It's scary.
That's right.
That's the mystery we're looking for.
So, when are you going to arrive?
Tomorrow.
Wait.
Ah, me too.
Isn't it too dangerous?
The adventure is dangerous.
That's why the captain and the others are here.
I think we should go back.
You're worried.
I got scared by the captain's scary face.
That's not it.
Ah, Zuboshi.
Scary face.
I told you that's not it.
You two are close, aren't you?
It's late.
Garen-san, would you like to come with me?
If you wish.
Hey, are you there?
Garen-senpai
Eri.
Where did you meet Garen-senpai?
Where did we meet?
At the pool.
What?
Next door.
Is that why you called me?
I've been curious about it for a long time.
I live alone in a luxury apartment.
When I go shopping, I buy luxury goods that even I hesitate to buy.
Did you go to school?
Yes.
I asked my father about it on the Internet.
When I went to see Garen-senpai, I couldn't find his birth place or school history.
It's impossible, isn't it?
What?
You're the one who's impossible.
Do you know what privacy is?
I know what you want to say.
But I want to know.
That's why you're always in the classroom.
Classroom has nothing to do with it.
I'm sure there's something, Garen-senpai.
It smells like a mysterious thing.
I can't wait for the first adventure tour of Trehanbun.
I'm so excited.
Hey, don't make me feel happy.
You're honest and pure.
Well, to be frank, you're a child.
I don't want to be told by you.
Garen-senpai
Yes.
Do you need anything, Eri?
Eri!
Let's go.
This is bad.
Is this a surprise party?
Of course not!
What are you going to do to the chief?
Aiko!
What are you doing?
Look!
What is it?
Something on his butt and neck...
It's like a machine.
That's gross. leben
Someone must have controlled him with this.
This is bad!
Hey, are you okay?
Are you okay?
Everyone!
What is it?
Let go!
I won't let you get away.
Teacher, why?
Too bad.
They failed, didn't they?
Sumeragi-san, I'll teach you.
People can be suspicious.
I don't like that!
I see.
Sumeragi-san, I'll teach you.
I can't believe I was able to take him to the infirmary.
I know where he went.
Let's take him to the infirmary.
Miss, let's take him back.
Not bad.
I'll continue.
Miss!
Of course you'll continue!
It was common sense to control a classmate who was brainwashed and attacked!
The purpose of that identity is to reveal the mystery of the mystery!
This is adventure! This is the real adventure!
Captain, if you pull back here, I'll go to my father and have him behead me!
Is that okay?
Eri!
It's a nightmare.
You go first and stop her.
I'm sorry for the trouble.
I was hired by Eri.
But if she says she's going, then there's nothing we can do.
There's nothing we can do?
What a troublesome kid.
There's nothing we can do.
It's a mystery.
To be continued