meet me at the
...
Sensei, why!?
Too bad. Those girls have failed.
...
Sumeragi-san, I'll tell you.
People can be suspicious.
I don't like that!
...
I'm sorry, but I don't know if it's the same thing.
I'm sorry.
It's the same thing.
Actually, I'm grateful that I have a friend who protects her.
But at this rate, I'll look at the tree and attack again.
I understand. I'm counting on you.
Roger.
I'm sorry.
When I close my eyes, I see the gap in my memory.
The nostalgic wind of that time blew.
Even if your bright smile is full of tears,
Even if you're about to burst, you're going to go beyond the present.
We were born in a time when we couldn't go back.
Even if everything is waiting for the future to pass in the footpath,
Just hold on tight to your unwavering feelings.
I believe in that endless love and walk.
Look.
I think they were controlling the people who were attached to Kei and Youzui.
I said that, though.
Judging from yesterday's situation, it's likely that Mr. Risako put this on.
That's what I said, too.
Don't say anything unnecessary.
It's because you say what I said as if you thought about it yourself.
That's what I thought, too.
You're lying. You said it was disgusting.
That's enough.
You're lying.
It's not a lie.
It's a lie.
It's true.
It's not a lie.
Karen.
This device will disappear naturally in a few days.
What?
I don't have any symptoms, so I don't need to worry.
How do you know that?
Senior, have you ever seen it before?
Where did you see it?
I think this device will disappear in a few days.
The way you say it has changed.
Then I'll go ahead.
Who is that girl?
Senior.
No, that's not it.
Approaching the destination point.
That's it.
We have arrived at the destination.
Everyone.
Congratulations.
This club is strange.
And there are many difficulties.
It's only the first time.
Don't say anything.
Yes.
The real adventure begins now.
Don't let your guard down.
Yes, sir.
Be careful not to let your guard down.
Yes.
I'm sorry.
Before we go on an adventure,
I would like to have a beach party.
Everyone.
Please drink a lot of water today.
Yes.
I have brought all the ingredients.
Thank you for your hard work.
You stay with the girls.
I hope nothing strange happens to you.
Yes, sir.
Where is the captain?
I'm investigating the seabed.
I see.
Yes, sir.
Wait.
Wow.
150 yards.
4 inch pin soba.
It's delicious.
But why golf?
It's a little strange, Karen.
He doesn't seem to have any old memories.
Loss of memory?
It's a problem if you don't have any memories.
Here it comes.
I'm hungry.
I'm home.
It's delicious.
It's amazing.
There is still a lot.
Please eat a lot.
It looks fun.
It's good.
Everyone knows about the incident last night, right?
Of course.
Why are you making me faint?
No one cares about the children sleeping on the ship.
Because it's an adventure.
No one cares about the incident.
Adventure.
It's natural to have one or two dangers.
What are you talking about?
That's right.
Well, it's okay.
Gusto, cook vegetables.
Yes.
Roast meat.
Yes, I'm home.
Season it.
Okay.
With love.
What is that?
Please cook this.
Yes, I'm happy.
It's a wild crab.
Where did you get that?
Can you eat that?
If it turns red, it's okay.
If it turns blue, there is poison.
Oh.
It's a wild crab grill.
Thank you for the food.
Wild crab poison?
This is bad.
Everyone, cover me.
This is...
Ellie.
Please take a look.
Garen, Gusto.
Are you okay?
Fortunately, I'm fine.
Gusto, take my bag.
Yes.
There is a sniper.
Where is he?
Teacher.
I knew it.
Gusto, dance and run.
Are you stupid?
If you do that, you will be shot.
Are you going to sleep?
You are crazy.
There is.
You have good skills, Sumeragi.
Ms. Risako.
I won't give it to Garen.
No.
Please give it to me.
It's dirty.
It's a surprise party from me.
Where is it?
Garen, Gusto, help me.
Help?
How?
I don't have a gun.
Do something with wisdom and courage.
Please leave it to me.
Anything is fine.
Thank you.
It's okay.
Four more.
What?
Hey.
What are you doing?
Garen.
Nice shot.
What?
It hurts.
I missed the shot.
Garen.
Nice shot.
I will stay.
What?
Where is the teacher?
By the way, that woman is not here.
Me?
When did it happen?
Garen.
I can't deal with you.
I don't need you.
Move.
Yes.
Hurry.
Welcome, Garen.
Sumeragi.
Even if you are a Salveger,
you don't have to do anything.
What are you talking about?
It's a mystery.
It's better to keep the secret.
There is a secret.
It's not enough to be happy.
What?
It doesn't make sense at all.
You are really stupid.
Yes.
I was stupid and it was bad.
Where am I?
What?
By the way,
you only did the north side of the school.
What?
It's enough to do only the north side.
I told you to do everything.
It's impossible to do everything alone.
It's a punishment to do even if it's impossible.
This punishment is too heavy.
Hey, are you okay?
Damn it.
Are you okay, Sumeragi?
It's time to end this.
Good night.
Hey.
Garen.
What are you doing?
I'm leaving.
You don't have to tie me up.
Oh,
who told you to suspect me?
Yes, yes.
I will listen to you.
Then,
let's talk.
Please forgive me.
I have my own situation.
I won't do that.
You look scared.
Answer me seriously.
Who told you to do that?
What's your purpose?
Don't talk like that.
Go home.
What are you talking about?
I've heard everything.
The next agent will come soon.
What?
This is the end of the adventure.
What is it, Garen?
It's a blow.
Senpai?
It's from yesterday.
It's too intense.
I'll tell the captain.
What's that?
A transmitter.
You can hear it, right?
It's you, right?
I remembered.
About the past.
About you too.
But it's not all.
I want to know about the time that disappeared.
I want to know the real me.
I'll decide the future myself.
So,
don't bother me anymore.
Please.
I'm sorry, but please hang out with me a little longer.
I'm sure there's an answer at the bottom of the sea.
I'm sure.
This again?
Shut up and do it.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
Do it.
Okay.
Well,
if you ask me about the news so far,
even your father will stop you.
It's a waste, right?
Of course.
This is the real thing.
I knew it.
I'll leave the members because it's impossible.
See you later.
Okay.
The girls I caught were in the warehouse.
You can do whatever you want.
Well,
the submarine is ready.
Okay.
All right.
Now,
let's go on an adventure of mystery and mystery.
Let's go.
It's light.
That's it.
Salveja,
get ready.
Roger that.
I'll leave the girls to you.
Okay.
Put the food here.
What?
It's food.
And
Marumi.
What?
Look over there.
Yes.
If you look at me, I'll kill you.
I didn't see that.
Hey, are you okay?
I'm fine.
What are you looking at?
It's not mine.
You're fine.
The kids these days are...
No.
It hit my hair.
It doesn't matter.
What are you talking about?
If one hair gets stuck, it will sink.
Don't yell at me.
I'll yell at you.
It's taking my life.
It's stuck.
Submarine, start attack.
Attack.
Hello, everyone in Japan.
I'm Eri Shinkai from Treasure Hunter.
We are now chasing the mystery and coming to the South Sea.
What are you doing?
To learn about the past,
you have to hurt the people around you.
And yourself.
To be continued...